Contact

0782446786 (Mobile) mutabazidavid@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/mutabazidavid-875561b2 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Web Design Search Engine Optimization (SEO) Microsoft Office

Languages

English (Professional Working) Swahili

Mutabazi David

Digital Marketing Manager

Kisoro, Western Region, Uganda

Summary

I am a software developer and also an expert in website designing and Web Development. I have good experience working with open-source frameworks like Laravel, Worpress, CakePHP, and Django. My major skills include HTML5, CSS3, PHP, and Javascript (with knowledge of Angular) as well as Database management systems like MySQL. My goal is to be the best at what I do and always find new ways to grow and improve my knowledge and skills as a software developer. I have been in the technology industry for 8 years now and looking forward to more challenging opportunities.

Experience

virungagorillatours.com/
Digital Marketing Specialist
January 2022 - Present (2 years 9 months)
Uganda

Am well versed with Web technologies / CMS / Digital Marketing and Graphics

www.virungacampsite.com
Digital Marketing Manager
January 2020 - July 2022 (2 years 7 months)
Kisoro, Western, Uganda

SEO-Serch Engine Optimisation Online social media Management Website update and Cyber Security

eShop Uganda Ltd

News letter / website manager September 2014 - January 2020 (5 years 5 months)

Social Media Marketing on all plat forms. Web & App development. Web/ Graphics design.

mashariki High School Computer Lab Assistant / Techncian January 2012 - February 2014 (2 years 2 months)

Page 1 of 2

Lab maintainance. which include networking, windows re-installatin.

Education

Makerere University

Bachelor's degree, C · (2009 - 2013)

Kampala International University

Bachelor of Computer Science · (January 2008 - November 2011)

Jinja College

A'Level, HSC · (2006 - 2008)

Busoga College Mwiri

UCE · (2002 - 2006)

Busoga College Mwiri